willowtreeapps.com 2019-10-25

# WillowTree | Privacy Policy

#### WillowTree, Inc. Privacy Policy

Welcome to WillowTree, Inc. We value your privacy, and we want to make sure you understand our policies regarding privacy and our website. We use our website to communicate with the public and potential customers about our products and services and to take in personal information by people and entities who wish to be in touch with us (the “Service”).

By accessing our website, you agree to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. We want you to know that your information, described below as both “personally identifying information” and “user information,” may be used for the following purposes: to provide and market our services to you, which includes operating the website; to improve the services we provide; to remember your preferences; to conduct in-house research; to prevent fraud or abuse; and to communicate with you and address your concerns.

If you use the website on behalf of a company, organization, government, or any other entity, then (a) “you” includes both you and that entity; and (b) you represent and warrant that you are legally authorized to consent to our collection, storage, use, and disclosure of the information we collect from you as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Registration and contact information

We provide certain services on our website, and other third-party websites we use, that require visitors to enter their personal information, such as contacting us, registering for our newsletters, or completing a job application. In these cases, we may collect certain personal information such as your name, your company name, email address, and your messages (“personally identifying information” or “PII”).

We use personally identifying information to operate and increase the effectiveness of our services and to communicate directly with you. We may make phone calls to you and send you emails messages, including information such as company newsletters, changes or updates to features of the Service, and technical and security notices.

#### Information we collect from all website visitors

_**User Information**_

We collect user information (“user information”) from your browser or mobile device each time you access the website. User information may include anonymous information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, information about your mobile device, referring/exit pages and URLs, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information. When you access our Service by or through a mobile device, we may receive or collect and store a unique identification number associated with your device, mobile carrier, device type and manufacturer, phone number, and, depending on your mobile device settings, your geographical location data, including GPS coordinates (e.g. latitude and/or longitude) or similar information regarding the location of your mobile device.

_**Internal Cookies**_

We use different types of cookies (both temporary and persistent) to make it easier for you to navigate the site, track usage of our site to improve your experience, and remember your preferences. Disabling cookies may limit your ability to use some areas of our site. If you would like to disable cookies, you can often do so with your browser settings. Check your browser or learn more here. Be aware that you may be unable to use certain features of our products if you disable cookies.

_**Third Party Providers**_

We may work with third party providers to store and receive data, reports, and other user information sent by your browser or mobile device, including the pages you visit, your use of our website, your use of third party applications, and other information that we may use to analyze and improve the Service. These third parties may use both temporary and persistent cookies.

These third party providers include, but are not limited to, Greenhouse, Inspectlet, Google Analytics, Mail Chimp, Vimeo, Embedly, Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, and Salesforce. We work with them in the following ways:

**greenhouse:** We use Greenhouse to manage job listings and receive applications for them. (<http://www.greenhouse.io/>)

**Inspectlet:** Inspectlet tracks IP addresses, session lengths, starting pages, and other information about user behavior on our website. (<http://www.inspectlet.com/>)

**Google Analytics:** We use Remarketing with Google Analytics to allow third-party vendors, including Google, to show ads on websites across the Internet. Our website and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies such as the Google Analytics cookie, and third-party cookies, to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our website and to report how ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our website. (<https://www.google.com/analytics/#?modal_active=none>)

**Mail Chimp:** We use Mail Chimp to improve our marketing efforts by tracking open rates for our emails and traffic to and from certain marketing campaign landing pages. (<https://mailchimp.com/>)

**Vimeo:** We use Vimeo to host video on our site, and Vimeo offers us viewership information and statistics about the videos we publish. (<https://vimeo.com/stats>)

**Embedly:** We use Embedly to embed certain external content into our site. Embedly tracks user interaction with their embedded content. (<http://embed.ly/analytics>)

**Facebook:** We use Facebook’s conversion measurement tools to track the effectiveness of our advertisements on Facebook. (<https://www.facebook.com/business/a/online-sales/conversion-tracking>)

**Twitter:** We use Twitter’s conversion measurement tools to track the effectiveness of our advertisements on Twitter. (<https://business.twitter.com/en/help/campaign-measurement-and-analytics/conversion-tracking-for-websites.html>)

**Salesforce:** We use Salesforce to compile and track personal information for our newsletter and for customer outreach, among other direct contact methods. (<https://www.salesforce.com/products/sales-cloud/overview/?d=70130000000lzaAAAQ>)

**LinkedIn:** We use LinkedIn to increase marketing and advertsing channels and recruit job candidates. (<https://www.linkedin.com/company/1099749/admin/>)

The collection and storage of your data by these third party service providers, as well as information on whether and how you can opt out of their collection and storage of your data, is governed by their privacy policies, which can be accessed at these sites:

Greenhouse: <http://www.greenhouse.io/privacy-policy>  
Inspectlet: <https://www.inspectlet.com/legal#privacy>  
Google: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>  
Embedly: <http://embed.ly/legal/privacy>  
Mail Chimp: <https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/> Vimeo: <https://vimeo.com/privacy>  
Salesforce: <https://www.salesforce.com/company/privacy/>  
Facebook: <https://www.facebook.com/full_data_use_policy>  
Twitter: <https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en> LinkedIn: <https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy>

_**Web Beacons**_

Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on our website or in our emails. We and third party partners may use web beacons (also known as clear gifs or web bugs), images, tags and scripts that help us and them better manage content on our site to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness, and to determine whether an email has been opened and acted upon.

_**Local Shared Objects and Flash Cookies**_

To personalize your visit, we may use local shared objects such as HTML5 to store your preferences such as volume control or to display content based on what you view on our website. Third party partners provide certain features on our sites and may display advertising based on your browsing activity using Flash cookies or HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing content stored locally using HTML5.

We may also use Flash cookies to collect information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of data stored, type of data stored, and way in which data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser usually will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for certain Flash cookies, click here.

#### Sharing information with third parties

We may share information in an aggregated and anonymous form that does not reasonably identify you directly as an individual or entity, in the ways described below. For further information on your choices regarding your information, see “Your Choices Regarding Your Information.”

We may share your information with other companies owned by or under common ownership as WillowTree, which also includes any subsidiaries, heirs, assigns, or acquirers. In addition to WillowTree and third parties, the following entities may use your personal information under this Policy: service providers that perform services on our or third parties’ behalf, which may include payment processing, content or service fulfillment, or providing analytics services; third parties, at your request; other parties in connection with any company transaction, such as a merger, sale of company assets or shares, reorganization, financing, change of control or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company or third party or in the event of bankruptcy or related or similar proceedings; and third parties as required to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, subpoena/court order, legal process or other governmental request, (b) investigate and defend ourselves against any third party claims or allegations, © protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of WillowTree, our users, or the public as required or permitted by law, and (d) detect, prevent or otherwise address criminal (including fraud or stalking), security, or technical issues.

#### Your choices regarding your information

**Marketing Communications**

If you do not wish to receive promotional emails, you can click the “unsubscribe” button on promotional email communications. Please note that you may not unsubscribe or opt out of non-promotional messages regarding your account, such as account verification, password requests, order confirmations, changes or updates to features of the Service, or technical and security notices.

**Data Retention**

At our discretion, we will retain all PII and user information that we collect. Please contact us if you wish us to remove your PII, at [info@willowtreeapps.com](mailto:info@willowtreeapps.com).

**Do-Not-Track**

Because we want to provide you with a personalized experience on the Service, we do not change our behavior based on a web browser’s Do Not Track signal.

#### Security and storage of information

WillowTree cares about the security of your information and uses commercially reasonable physical, administrative, and technological safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of all information we collect and that we share with our service providers. However, we cannot make a 100% guarantee of the security of our systems. If information under our control is compromised, we will take commercially reasonable steps to investigate the situation. Where appropriate, we will notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised. We may take other steps in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations.

Your information collected through the Service may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which WillowTree or its subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers, heirs, assigns, or acquirers maintain facilities.

If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we may transfer your information to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction.

While we will attempt to maintain the confidentiality of all PII submitted, we disclaim any liability for any claims or damages related to any unauthorized disclosure or interception of any information that you submit to us. For your own privacy and protection, we encourage you not to include sensitive personal information in any emails you send to us.

#### Persons under the age of 13

Our Service is not designed for those younger than 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not use our Service and please do not send us any information about yourself. If we discover that we have collected any PII from a child under the age of 13, we will remove that information from our records.

#### Links to third-party websites

In addition to the third party providers above, the Service may contain links to and from other third party websites of our business partners and various contact management services. Please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies. Please check the individual policies before you submit any information to those websites.

#### Notice to California residents

If you are a resident of California, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 allows you to request information regarding the disclosure of your PII by us to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. This applies only to their activities within the State of California. To make such a request, please contact us at [info@willowtreeapps.com](mailto:info@willowtreeapps.com).

#### Acceptance of this privacy policy

By using our website, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our website. We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version will govern our use of your information and will always be at <https://willowtreeapps.com/privacy-policy>. To keep up to date on revisions to this Privacy Policy, we suggest that you regularly check this web page. By continuing to access or use the website, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy, as revised from time to time.

#### Contacting us

If you have questions about this Policy, please email us at [info@willowtreeapps.com](mailto:info@willowtreeapps.com) or write to us at 107 5th St., SE, Charlottesville, VA 22902.

#### Last revision date

This Privacy Policy was last revised on, and effective as of MARCH 21, 2017.
